好的
Okay.
我走了
I'm leaving.
罗西
Rosy...
等等
Wait.
我就在这里的角落里下车
I'll get off just here in the corner.
你到了
There you go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 你叫什么名字 - 罗西
- What's your name? - Rosy.
我叫詹姆斯
I'm James.
那么你就是照片上的那个女孩
So you're the girl in the photos?
是的 那是我
Yes. That's me.
好吧 我很荣幸
Well, I'm honored.
别这样
Don't be.
马蒂真的没那么好
Marty's really not that good.
好吧 我不会告诉他你这么说的
Well, I won't tell him you said that,
因为他是我最好的朋友
because he's my best friend.
他也是我的
He's mine, too.
但他从来没有提到过你
But he's never mentioned you.
得了吧 他为什么要提
Come on, why would he?
他到底在哪里
Where is he anyway?
马蒂
Marty.
你是个模特吗
Are you a model?
天啊 不是 不是
God, no. No.
我是一个女演员
I'm an actress.
哦
Oh.
非正式的 我还在上学
Unofficially. I'm in school for it.
这是个艰难的行业
It's a tough business.
是的 我可以处理它
Yeah, I can handle it.
我是好斗的
I'm feisty.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I got that.
我可以说点什么吗
Can I say something?
是的
Yes.
你真是太漂亮了
You are absolutely beautiful.
他已经结婚了
He's married.
- 马特 - 他已经结婚了
- Mart. - He's married.
我们正找你呢
We were just looking for you.
- 是的 - 好吧 真是时候
- Yeah. - Well, just in time.
那么 这是你的女朋友吗
So, is this your girlfriend?
这是我的缪斯女神
This is my muse.
哦 哦 好吧
Oh. Oh, okay.
这是不是会让我们感到尴尬
Is that gonna make this awkward?
让什么尴尬
Make what awkward?
我们的友谊
Our friendship.
快离开这里
Get out of here.
去哪里
Where?
滚蛋
Scram.
来吧 现在
Come on, now.
安定下来
Settle down.
我喜欢这个节目 伟大的工作
I loved the show. Great job.
谢谢你 谢谢你的到来
Thank you. Thank you for coming.
谢谢你的罗西
Thank you for Rosy.
不客气
You're welcome.
你检查了角落里的迷你模型吗
Did you check out the miniatures by the corner there?
是的 我喜欢它们
Yeah, I loved them.
- 看看他们吧 - 我会的
- Check 'em out. - I will.
- 看看他们吧 - 他们值得重新审视
They're worth revisiting.
哦 好的 好的
Oh, okay. Okay.
谢谢你 詹姆斯 再见了
Thank you, James. See you soon.
回头见
See you around.
来吧 不要回头看
Come on. Don't look back.
我没有
I'm not.
你不会想和那个人说话的
You do not wanna be talking to that guy.
他是谁
Who is he?
他是一个正在恢复的酒鬼
He's a recovering alcoholic,
- 赌徒 性瘾者 - 住手
- gambler, sex addict... - Stop.
救命
Help!
救命啊
不要害怕
Don't be scared.
我很抱歉 那是氯仿的作用
I'm sorry. That's the chloroform.
不 走开
No! Get away!
你是谁
Who are you?
救命啊
Help!
拜托谁来帮帮我
Please! Somebody help me!
来人啊
Somebody!
这是你的钱包和你的外套
Here's your purse and your jacket.
我还在梳妆台上给你留了一些我的东西
And I left a few things of mine in the dresser for you.you.
这是一个内置摄像头的显示器
Here's a monitor with a built-in camera.
这样如果你需要什么
So that if you ever need anything,
你可以直接告诉我
you can just let me know.
你看起来很沮丧
You seem upset.
所以我去给你买点吃的
So I'm gonna go get you something to eat,
我相信你会感觉好些
and I'm sure you're gonna feel better.
只是 你知道 冷静下来
Just, you know... Just calm down,
让自己像在家里一样
make yourself at home.
你知道 好吗
You know... Okay?
你知道我需要你的爱
♪ You know I need Your love ♪
你对我的控制力
♪ You got that hold over me ♪
只要我有你的爱
♪ Long as I got your love ♪
你知道我永远不会离开
♪ You know that I'll never leave ♪
当我想让你分享我的生活时
♪ When I wanted you To share my life ♪
我毫不怀疑自己的想法
♪ I had no doubt in my mind ♪
我给你带来了鸡蛋和鳄梨
I brought you eggs and avocados...
不
No!
我知道这很疯狂
I know this is crazy.
我是一个善良的人
I'm a good person,
我带你来的这里
and I brought you here
来和我在一起
to be with me,
因为我只是想让你了解我
because I just want you to get to know me.
我有什么资格说我想要你回来
♪ Who am I to say I want you back? ♪
当你从来都不是我的 可以送人的时候
♪ When you were never mine To give away ♪
我等待了很久 很长一段时间
♪ I was waiting For a long, long time ♪
让你有同样的感觉
♪ For you to feel the same ♪
你是谁 可以这样看着我
♪ Who are you to look At me like that? ♪
你还需要说些什么吗
♪ Is there something more You need to say? ♪
我没有爱过你 在一个很长很长的时间
♪ I haven't loved you In a long, long time ♪
那么 为什么我觉得这种方式
♪ So why do I feel this way? ♪
你能听到我的心跳吗
♪ Can you hear my heartbeat? ♪
请不要站在离我这么近的地方
♪ Please don't stand So close to me ♪
你能听到我的心跳仍然跳动强烈
♪ Can you hear my heartbeat Still beating strong? ♪
你发现它好吗
Did you find it okay?
嗯 嗯
Uh-huh.
你会演奏这些乐器吗
You play those instruments?
不 那些是用来装饰的
No, those are for decoration.
对不起 我只是有点害羞
Sorry, I'm just being shy...
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
那么 你是个音乐家
So, you're a musician.
不是
No.
我是拍纪录片的
I make documentaries.
你从来没有告诉过我你是做电影的
You never told me you were in the movie business.
嗯 你从来没有问过
Well, you never asked.
没错
True.
关于什么的记录片
Documentaries about what?
音乐
Music...
哦
Oh.
这就对了
There you go.
哇
Wow.
那么 我有什么问题吗
So... what's wrong with me?
你是什么意思没什么
What do you mean? Nothing.
你的婚姻不幸福吗
Are you unhappily married?
哦 对了 她在哪里
Oh... Where is she, by the way?
我没料到你会这么主动 我
I didn't expect you to be so forward. I...
只是喜欢你 很想再见到你
just liked you and was curious to see you again.
你没有回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question.
我
I...
我想我犯了一个错误
think I made a mistake.
你只是在取笑我
You're just making fun of me.
我知道这整个年龄的事情是不应该重要的 但是
And I know this whole age thing is not supposed to matter, but...matter, but...
所以你想和我上床
So you want to fuck me?
我很抱歉 我想你应该去
I'm sorry. I think you should go.
詹姆斯
James...
让我们重新开始吧
Let's start over.
罗西 已经两天了
Rosy, it's been two days.
我并没有指望这个 我知道你一定很饿
I wasn't counting on this. I know you must be hungry.
你就尝一口好吗
Will you just try one bite?
求你了 就吃一口吧
Please, just try one bite.
不要对我这样做
Don't do this to me.
这很好
It's good.
你看
Look...
你看起来很好
you seem nice.
我也明白了
And I get it.
你认为你不能让我走 因为我会直接去找警察
You think you can't let me go because I'll go straight to the police.straight to the police.
但我不会的
But I won't.
我们可以解决这个问题
We can fix this.
这将是像它从来没有发生过
It'll be like it never happened.
我是说
I mean that.
你可以开车送我回家
You can just drive me home
没有人会注意到我已经离开了
and no one will ever notice that I was gone.
这将是我们的秘密
It'll be our secret.
求你了
Please?
对不起 这只是
Sorry. It's just...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能吃你那该死的食物
I can't eat your fucking food!
呣
Hmm?
我是个素食主义者
I'm a vegan.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
谢谢你的询问
Thanks for asking.
我叫道格
My name's Doug.
你是罗西吗
And you're Rosy?
你怎么知道我的名字
How'd you know my name?
在这里
Here.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
- 我得去尿尿  - 噢
- I have to pee. - Oh.
哦
Oh.
去吧
Go ahead.
好的
Okay.
所以你把卫生间的门拿走了
So you took the bathroom door away?
是的 我做了
Yes, I did.
这样你就不会把自己锁在里面了
So you wouldn't lock yourself in.
为什么是我
Why me?
你说什么
Pardon?
你为什么选我来绑架
Why'd you pick me to kidnap?
因为我认为我们之间有某种联系
Because I think we have a connection.
什么
A what?
一种联系
A connection.
如果我们都不认识对方 怎么可能有联系
How can we have a connection if we don't even know each other?each other?
人们每天都会在一些地方看到对方
People see each other in places every day
他们会想 这可能是我要找的人
and they think, "That could be the person for me."
你知道 人们会找我的
You know, people are gonna be looking for me.
嗨 罗西
Hi, Rosy.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
嗨
Hi.
呃
Uh...
我要走了 而且要离开一段时间
I'm gonna leave and I'm gonna be gone for a while.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要出去工作
I'm heading out to work.
不过我今晚会很晚回来
I'll be back late tonight though.
我就在这里
I'll be here.
你说什么
What did you say?
你好
Hello.
你在这里工作吗
Do you work here?
是的
Yeah.
我可以跟你的经理说话吗
May I speak to your manager, please?
我们正在调查一个失踪的女孩
We're investigating a missing girl.
呃 你好
Uh, hello?
我是戈丁医生
This is Dr. Godin here.
你好 戈丁博士 你好
Hello, Dr. Godin. Hi.
嗨 我很高兴我终于找到你了
Hi. I'm glad I finally reached you.
我已经留了好几条信息
I've left several messages.
嗯 我一直住在我奶奶家
Well, I've been staying at my grandmother's house.
我有一个最新消息
I have an update.
你祖母的生命体征已经有了很大的改善
Your grandmother's vitals have been improving a lot.
我相信她很有可能恢复知觉
I'm confident that she could very well regain consciousness.consciousness.
什么
What?
这不是一个承诺 只是 它可以这样发展
It's not a promise, it's just that... It could go that way.that way.
现在 已经有了一些损伤
Now, there has been some damage.
氧气
The oxygen...
有什么损害
What's the damage?
我不确定她是否还能再走路
I'm not sure if she'll ever be able to walk again.
而且她肯定会有说话的困难
And she will certainly have difficulty speaking.
你应该来和我们见面 讨论一下前景
You should come meet with us to discuss the prospects.prospects.
在康复之后 你要考虑的事情包括
Following rehabilitation, you have to think about things like...things like...
等等 你是说
Wait, you're saying...
你的家要能坐轮椅
...your home to be wheelchair accessible.
你是说 我可以让她回来
You're saying that I could have her back?
这看起来更有可能 我只能这么说
It's looking a lot more likely. That's all I can say.
我可以问你一件事吗
Can I ask you something?
好的
Yep.
嗯
Um...
是
It's...
她会不会像 嗯
Would she be like, um...
对她周围发生的事情有所认识
cognizant of things going on around her?
你是什么意思
How do you mean?
哦 来吧
Oh, come on!
卧槽
Fuck!
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我给你买了些外卖
I picked you up some takeout,
我给你买了一些健康的零食 让你在下面吃
and I got you some healthy snacks to have down here.
哦 谢谢 你能把它们放在梳妆台上吗
Oh, thanks. Can you just put them over there on the dresser?dresser?
其实我现在不怎么饿
I'm actually not that hungry right now.
- 这是什么 - 这是什么
- What's this? - What?
在这里 这是什么
Here. What is this?
哦 那个 哈
Oh. That. Hah!
嗯 那是 这就是我在这里的时间
Um, that's... That's how long I've been here for.
我希望你不要介意
I hope you don't mind.
我只是在记录
I'm just keeping track.
嗯
Hmm.
花瓶在哪里
Where's the vase?
就在地板上 我把它搬走了
Just there on the floor. I moved it.
你今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
很好
Good.
我很累
I'm pretty tired.
我想我今晚就去睡觉了
I think I'm just gonna go to bed tonight.
你看起来很疲惫
You look pretty spent yourself.
是的 你可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.
晚安
Good night.
'Night.
我忘了拿这个
I forgot to grab this.
我奶奶可能会搬来和我们一起住
My grandmother may be moving in with us.
太好了
Great.
她是什么样的人
What is she like?
她很好
She's great.
我肯定
I'm sure.
她知道我在这里吗
Does she know that I'm here?
我还没有完全搞清楚 但
I haven't quite worked all that out yet, but...
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
我很抱歉 我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
请不要伤害我
Please don't hurt me!
Please don't hurt me.
你刚才想做什么
What were you trying to do?
嗯
Huh?
你刚才想做什么
What were you trying to do?
我是想出去
I was trying to get out.
它看起来像什么
What does it look like?
你不能出去 那些窗户甚至不能打开
You can't get out. Those windows don't even open.
什么
What?
那你为什么把它们封起来
Why'd you board them up, then?
我今天过的很辛苦
I've had a really hard day.
而我最不需要的就是你这样的狗屎
And the last thing I need is for you to pull shit like this.like this.
哦 你有一个艰难的一天
Oh, you've had a hard day?
你可以出去做你想做的事
You get to go out there and do whatever you want,
只要你想
whenever you want.
我? 我被困在这里
I? I am stuck here,
整天都是如此
all day long.
而我一天中唯一美好的部分就是我睡觉的时候
And the only good part of my day is when I go to sleep,sleep,
因为那时 我知道我将会撑到明天
because then, then I know that I'm gonna make it till tomorrow.till tomorrow.
好了 这是最后一次了 我不是要伤害你
All right. For the last time. I'm not trying to hurt you.you.
我只是想照顾好你
I'm just trying to take care of you.
我想这是很清楚的
I think that's pretty clear.
- 照顾我 - 是的
- Take care of me? - Yes.
看看我
Look at me!
我已经很久没有洗过澡了
I haven't had a shower in forever.
我闻起来像狗屎
I smell like shit.
你看到我的头发有多油了吗
Do you see how greasy my hair is?
嗯
Huh?
那间浴室里只有一个水槽
There's only a sink in that bathroom.
我 我可以给你香皂
I... I could give you soap.
但是 是的 我没有想到这一点
But, yeah, I didn't think of that.
我没有想到这一点 只是 你知道
I didn't think of that. Just, you know...
是的 你没有想到 当你正在进行
Yeah, it didn't occur to you that while you were havinghaving
你那漂亮、温暖、舒适的小淋浴时
your nice, warm, little cozy showers
我可能也需要它们
that I might be needing them, too?
我已经被淹没了 我一直在处理很多事情
I've been very overwhelmed, and I've been dealing with a lot,with a lot,
而且很多事情发生得非常快
and a lot has happened really fast.
所以这可能与此有关
So it has something to do with that, probably.
我不在意
I don't care.
当你考虑你的需求时
When you think about your needs,
你需要试着考虑一下我的需求
you need to try and think about mine.
好吧 是的
All right, yeah.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
度过一天的最好方法
The best way to get through your day
是专注于你所拥有的美好事物
is to focus on the good things you have,
而不是坏事
not the bad.
这七个步骤
The seven steps.
我是谁我在哪里
Who am I? Where am I?
我和谁在一起
Who am I with?
我想要什么
What do I want?
我怎么做才能得到我想要的东西
What do I do to get what I want?
刚才又发生了什么好吗
And what just happened? Okay?
我是一个谜
I am an enigma.
你是一个谜
You're an enigma?
- 我是一个谜 - 你是一个谜
- I am an enigma. - You're an enigma.
你很紧张
You're nervous.
我很紧张
I'm nervous?
你很紧张
You're nervous.
我很紧张
I'm nervous.
说点性感的话
Say something sexy.
什么时候表演
What time's the show?
9:00
我真的很兴奋
I'm really excited.
好吧 我们要忙着拍一晚上
Well, we're gonna be busy shooting all night.
我不认为这将是适当的
I don't think it'd be appropriate
我不认为我带一个女孩一起去
for me to bring a girl along.
我给你我的信用卡 你可以在城里走走
I'll give you my credit card, and you can walk around town.around town.
我在新泽西要做什么呢
What am I gonna do in Jersey?
她漂亮吗
Is she pretty?
她是个孩子
She's a kid.
唱片公司把她从加拿大的某个电视舞蹈比赛中挑选出来
The label picked her up from some televised dance competition in Canada.competition in Canada.
为什么 她多大了
Why? How old is she?
我想她才15岁
I think she's 15.
这很淫秽
That's obscene.
她有一个职业生涯 你正在制作一部纪录片
She has a career that you're making a documentary about,about,
而我就像一个完全的无名小卒
and I'm like a total nobody.
来吧
Come on.
我有一个相当好的朋友 他是一个人才代表
I have a pretty good friend who's a talent rep,
我可以介绍你 当我们回来
and I can introduce you when we get back.
他是一个相当直率的人
He's a pretty straight shooter.
詹姆斯 你把我当成你的女朋友吗
James, do you think of me as your girlfriend?
你想成为吗
You want to be?
是的
Yeah.
如果你要上楼的话 你得让我把你的脚踝拷起来
You're gonna have to let me cuff your ankles if you're gonna go upstairs.you're gonna go upstairs.
我觉得这很荒唐
I think that's ridiculous.
我在下面的时候 你至少可以把这些东西拿下来吗
Will you at least take these off when I'm down here?
这样我就能更容易地保持理智
It will be much easier for me to maintain my sanity
和使用卫生间
and to use the bathroom.
我们将拭目以待
We'll see.
来吧
Come on.
你有一个监视器来监视我
You've got a monitor to watch me.
也许吧
Maybe.
好吧 至少我可以在洗澡的时候把它们拿下来吗
Well, can I at least take them off while I shower?
我不会戴着手铐跑掉的
I'm not gonna run away with my legs cuffed.
束缚我让你兴奋吗
Does it turn you on to restrain me?
嗯
Hmm?
那个唱片机能用吗
Does that record player work?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
哇
Wow.
这是个相当大的房子
This is a pretty big house.
什么 你现在要给我洗澡吗
What, are you gonna wash me now?
你从外面把门锁上了
You're locking the door from the outside?
是的
Correct.
我怎么知道我一脱光了你就不会进来了
How do I know you're not gonna come in once I'm naked?naked?
罗西
Rosy?
是的
Yes.
我需要担心你会在里面自杀吗
Do I need to worry about you killing yourself in there?there?
我没有自杀倾向 屁眼
I'm not suicidal, arsehole.
你奶奶会来吗
Is your grandmother coming?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
她不会想知道为什么所有的窗户都被封死了吗
Isn't she gonna wonder why all the windows are boarded up?boarded up?
嗯 我会告诉她是医生的命令
Um, I'll tell her that the doctor ordered it.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
她生病了吗
Is she sick?
那么 你要怎么解释那个戴着手铐的女孩
Well, how are you gonna explain the handcuffed girl
不允许在花园里闲逛
that's not allowed to stroll the garden?
你必须呆在楼下
You'll have to stay downstairs.
我的洗澡水怎么办
What about my baths?
我会想办法的
I'll figure it out.
还有 道格
Also, Doug...
什么事
Yes?
我 我真的很感激
I... I really appreciate
你给我的牙刷和牙膏
the toothbrush and toothpaste you gave me,
还有那把可怕的发刷
and the horrific hairbrush.
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
但由于我要在这里待上一段时间
But since I'm gonna be here for a while,
我还需要一些东西
I'm gonna need a few more things.
比如卫生棉条
Like tampon.
我还需要我的吸入器
And I need my inhaler.
我想要一个吹风机
I'd like a blowdryer,
而且我肯定需要更多的衣服
and I definitely need more clothes,
比如几条内裤 一些鞋子
like a few pair of panties, some shoes.
哦 有些书就更好了
Oh, some books would be nice.
我最喜欢的作家是玛丽-麦克莱恩
My favorite author is Mary McClain.
还有 能不能也买些化妆品
And would it be possible to get some makeup as well?
在回顾了个人和法律方面的后果后
Having reviewed the personal and legal ramifications
关于生命终结的决定
regarding the end of life decision,
现在让我们讨论一下更受欢迎的替代结果
let's now discuss the much preferred alternative outcome,outcome,
以及你将不得不采取的措施
and the measures you'll have to take
如果凯瑟琳真的从植物人的状态中醒来
if Katherine does indeed wake up from her vegetative state.state.
我个人认为这可能是任何一天
Which I personally think could be any day now.
一种选择是将她安置在养老院
One option is setting her up in a nursing home.
没有
No.
好吧
Well...
如果你想把她带回家 我
if you'd rather bring her home, I...
我建议你雇一个看护人或一个护士
I recommend that you hire a caretaker or a nurse
来管理她的用药
to administer her medication.
这里有一些信息 你可能会发现有帮助
Here's some information you might find helpful.
基本准备工作
Basic preparations,
预期费用
expected costs.
我正在和我告诉你的那个女孩约会
I'm seeing that girl that I told you about.
她是 她是
She's... She's...
她是个好帮手 但是
She's a handful. But...
我爱上了她
I'm in love with her.
我很害怕我没有以正确的方式做这件事
I'm scared I'm not doing this in the right way.
我希望你能告诉我
I wish you could tell me.
谢谢你做的一切 戈丁医生
Thank you for everything, Dr. Godin.
你确定
Are you sure
你不需要更多的时间来考虑这个问题吗
you don't need some more time to think this through?
我已经想清楚了
I've thought it through.
关掉它
Turn it off.
天啊你能敲门吗
Jesus! Could you knock?
对不起
Sorry.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我的祖母去世了
My grandmother died.
什么
What?
怎么死的
How?
她中风了
She got a stroke.
你怎么了
What's the matter with you?
没什么
Nothing.
那么 我还得呆在下面吗
So, do I still have to stay down here?
这就是你要说的
That's all you have to say?
真的吗
Really?
我想抱抱你 但你也许应该
I'd hug you, except that you should probably
想想你现在的感觉
think about the way you're feeling right now
就是我父母对我的感觉
is how my parents are feeling about me.
等等 回来
Wait, come back!
该死的
Goddamn it!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
听着 我真的
Look, I really
诚实地想见见她
wanted honestly to meet her.
只是我觉得我在这下面快要窒息了
It's just I feel like I'm suffocating down here.
它是如此的黑暗
It's so dark.
你从来没有对一个人有过感觉吗
Have you never had a feeling for someone
从你见到他们的那一刻起
from the second you met them?
是的
Yes.
但它必须是双向的
But it has to be both ways.
如果你从来没有机会发现 你怎么知道呢
How do you know if you never get a chance to find out?out?
你想要什么
What do you want?
你想和我约会吗在这地下室里
You wanna date me? Here in the basement?
我不知道你把它叫做什么 但我只是想要一个机会
I don't know what you call it, but I just want a chance.chance.
好吧
Fine.
但我也想要一个机会
But I want a chance, too.
为了什么
For what?
你的信任
Your trust.
我不想一直被困在这里
I don't wanna be stuck down here all the time.
我们可以一起出去玩
We can hang out,
但我想在楼上做
but I wanna do it upstairs.
让我考虑一下
Let me think about it.
没有信任就不能有关系
You can't have a relationship without trust.
那么 你有过女朋友吗
So, have you ever had a girlfriend?
呃
Uh...
没有
No.
为什么
Why?
我 呃
I'm, uh...
不太善于交际
not the best at socializing,
而且我从来没有遇到过我喜欢的人
and I've just never met anyone that I liked.
所以你以前从未做过这样的事情
So you've never done anything like this before?
你做错了
You're doing it wrong.
我可以做吗
Can I do it?
我喜欢生火
I love building fires.
好的
Okay.
当然可以
Sure.
你有男朋友吗
Do you have a boyfriend?
如果我有呢
What if I did?
除了外出 还有其他认识人的方法 你知道的
There are other ways of meeting people, you know, besides going out.besides going out.
对我来说没那么简单
It's not that simple for me.
我现在的生活离我想象中的样子真的差得很远
I'm really far behind from where I thought I'd be in my life by now.my life by now.
我也是
Me too.
那么你是做什么的
So what do you do?
呃 我在一家餐馆工作
Uh, I work in a restaurant.
所以 当你把我一个人留在这里时 你就去那里
So that's where you go when you leave me here alone.
我奶奶希望我和一个好女孩在一起
My grandmother wanted me to be with a nice girl.
她本来可以活下来的
She could have survived,
我让他们把她从生命维持器上取下来
and I told them to take her off life support.
你为什么要这样做
Why did you do that?
如果由我决定 我当然会让她活着
If it were up to me, I would have kept her alive, of course.course.
但她不会想这样回来的 我了解她
But she wouldn't want to come back like that. I know her.her.
那么你就做了正确的事
Then you did the right thing.
好的 晚安
Okay, good night.
还有 道格
Also, Doug.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm?
尽管我们非常不同
Even though we're very different,
我也知道孤独的感觉
I do know what it's like to feel alone.
我以前从来没有这样做过
I've never done this before.
什么
What?
呃
Uh...
你问我是否从未做过这个
You asked if I've never done this before.
好吧
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
我今天有一个试演
I had an audition today.
我想我让自己出丑了
I think I made a fool of myself.
表演课不是很有帮助吗
Aren't acting classes helping?
嗯
Mm.
它让你对学校感到内疚
It makes you feel guilty about school.
为什么
Why?
我不知道 我只是
I don't know, I just...
我只是不知道我是否足够想要它
I just don't know if I want it badly enough.
就像 有什么意义
Like, what's the point
在学费上欠下这么多债
of racking up all this debt in tuition?
你知道 它会变得更好
You know, it's gonna get better.
嗯 我
Well, I...
有什么意义呢
What's the point?
你说完了吗
You done?
- 嗯 嗯 - 好啊
- Mm-hmm. - Okay.
你知道 亲爱的 你所做的只是抱怨
You know, honey, all you ever do is whine
并为在这个行业的发展感到焦虑
and have anxiety over making it in the business.
这99%是你无法控制的
It's 99% out of your control.
这不是我所做的
That's not what I do.
你读了我给你的那本书吗
Did you read that book I gave you?
还没有
Not yet.
我可以问你一些问题吗
Can I ask you something?
可以
Yes.
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
我喜欢和你在一起的时间
I love spending time with you.
你爱你的妻子吗
Do you love your wife?
我在很多关系中都说过 我爱你
I've said "I love you" in plenty of relationships.
我的问题是 呃
My problem is, uh...
我们最终会厌烦别人
we eventually get sick of people.
这真是个愤世嫉俗的说法
That's a really cynical thing to say.
你为什么不厌烦我
Why don't you get sick of me?
进来吧
Come in.
- 道格 - 什么
- Doug? - Yes?
来这里
Come here.
你认为你是适合我的人吗
You think you're the guy for me?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
那我就告诉你怎么做
Then I'm gonna show you how it's done.
而且我们会发现
And we're gonna find out.
你这话是什么意思
What do you mean by that?
你要带我出去约会
You're gonna take me out on a date.
一个正式的约会
On a proper date.
我们要和对方交谈
And we're gonna talk to each other.
我们要告诉对方一切
And we're gonna tell each other everything.
我希望你能给我一些东西
And I want you to get me something.
一份礼物
A present.
什么样的礼物
What kind of present?
袜子
Stockings.
就是那种
The kind that
到这里来的
come up to here.
上面是松散的
And that are loose at the top.
复古的那种
The vintage kind.
我还想要一些吊袜带
And I want some garters with them as well.
我的白天比我的夜晚更黑暗
♪ My days are darker Than my nights ♪
我的世界是黑色的 没有灯光
♪ My world is black There are no lights ♪
我的眼睛是盲目的 我不能看到
♪ My eyes are blind I cannot see ♪
你为我点燃的世界在哪里
♪ Where's the world You lit for me? ♪
画的东西从过去
♪ Painted things From the past ♪
是褪色的东西 不能持久
♪ Are faded things That couldn't last ♪
所有神奇的颜色在哪里
♪ Where are All the magic colors ♪
曾经照亮我的路
♪ That used to light my way? ♪
所有神奇的颜色都在哪里
♪ Where are All the magic colors? ♪
我必须找到昨天的那些彩虹
♪ I must find those rainbows Of yesterday ♪
我的草地是绿色的 天空是蓝色的
♪ My grass was green The sky was blue ♪
当我和你分享这个世界时
♪ When I shared The world with you ♪
但现在颜色变成了灰色
♪ But now the colors Turn to gray ♪
我的彩虹世界逃之夭夭
♪ My rainbow world Escaped away ♪
灰色的阴影和黑色的阴影
♪ Shades of gray And shades of black ♪
我是如此孤独 我想回去
♪ I'm so alone I wanna go back ♪
回到所有神奇的颜色
♪ Back to All the magic colors ♪
曾经照亮我的路
♪ That used to light my way ♪
所有神奇的颜色在哪里
♪ Where are All the magic colors? ♪
我必须找到昨天的那些彩虹
♪ I must find those rainbows Of yesterday ♪
晦
Hi.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
对不起 我的地方是这样一个烂摊子
Sorry, my place is such a mess.
这很好
That's fine.
哦 我只是掩盖了这一点 所以 我看起来的方式是一个惊喜
Oh, I only covered that so that the way that I looked is a surprise.looked is a surprise.
我想 别担心
I figured. Don't worry about it.
我知道你为什么这么做
I knew why you did it.
那么 你要带我去哪里
So... where are you taking me?
呃 去饭厅
Uh, to the dining room.
啊 太棒了
Ah! Fantastic.
从未去过
Never been.
我有时确实想念肉
I do miss meat sometimes.
你想吃一口吗这里的肉很不错
Do you want a bite? The cut here is fantastic.
好吧 我试试
Okay. I'll try it.
但不要告诉任何人
But don't tell anyone.
嗯
Mmm.
这很好
It's good.
我只是
I just...
我只是太喜欢动物了
I just love animals too much.
那么你绝对应该成为吃肉的支持者
Then you should definitely be a proponent of meat eating,eating,
因为一旦我们毁了我们的星球
because once we ruin our planet,
我们将不得不搬到另一个星球
we'll have to move to another one.
而唯一能说服人们为动物腾出空间的东西
And the only thing that'll convince people to make room for the animalsroom for the animals
就是他们有机会吃它们
is their chance to eat them.
那么你的父母住在哪里
So where do your parents live?
我父亲从小就不在身边 我母亲
My father was never around growing up, and my mother...mother...
自杀了
killed herself.
为什么
Why?
我不知道 我当时非常年轻
I don't know. I was very young.
我想我是幸运的
I think I'm lucky.
否则可能会非常痛苦
It might have been very painful otherwise.
嗯
Hmm.
我的父母可能甚至不知道我失踪了
My parents probably don't even know that I'm missing.
我怀疑这一点
I doubt that.
我是说 他们有一些钱
I mean, they have some money.
他们并不富裕或什么的
They're not filthy rich or anything,
但他们可以把我送到学校
but they could have put me through school.
我只是 我只是不认为他们很喜欢我
I just... I just don't think they like me very much.
说得好听一点
And to put it kindly,
我妈妈很单纯 我爸爸是个自恋狂
my mom is simple, my father's a narcissist,
所以我不得不自己做一切事情
so I've had to do everything myself.
我觉得这很累人
And I find it pretty exhausting.
那么 你认为警察在找我吗
So, you think the police are looking for me?
你希望他们是吗
Do you want them to be?
你是一个相当好的厨师
You're a pretty good cook.
你是你餐厅的主厨吗
Are you the chef at your restaurant?
嗯 我算是一个万能的人 我是个副厨师
Um, I'm sort of an everything man. I'm a sous-chef,
我是副主厨 我帮助服务
and I help serve.
但我的经理说 他将及时把我调到厨房
But my manager said that he'll move me into the kitchen in time.kitchen in time.
你是做什么的
What do you do?
哦 我是个演员
Oh... I'm an actress.
- 一个女演员
- An actress? - Mm-hmm.
我可以看到 你会是一个非常棒的女演员
I can see that. You'd be a really fantastic actress.
我很想在电影屏幕上看到你的脸
I'd love to see your face on a movie screen.
哇
Wow.
我的意思是
I mean...
你为什么不开你自己的餐馆
Why don't you open your own restaurant?
你是个很好的厨师 不能只为人们服务
You're too good of a cook to just be serving people.
我刚刚吃了一块牛排 看在上帝的份上
I've just had a piece of steak, for Christ sake.
这不是那么简单
It's not that simple.
嗯 偷一个人并不简单
Mm... Stealing a person is not simple,
但你已经做到了
yet you've done that.
你只需要足够渴望它
You just have to want it badly enough.
恐惧是愚蠢的
Fear is stupid.
大多数遗憾也是如此
And so are most regrets.
你知道吗 一开始我很害怕带走你
You know, I was scared to take you at first,
但后来我想 如果它是注定的 它将是
but then I thought, if it's meant to be, it'll be.
好吧 你从来没有告诉过我我很漂亮
Well, you never tell me I'm pretty.
- 呃 我觉得你是
- Uh, I think you're... - No, don't. Don't.
因为如果你现在说 就意味着你不是真心的
Because if you say it now, it means that you don't mean it.mean it.
所以这不算数
So it's not gonna count.
你得告诉我怎么做这些事
You need to tell me how to do these things.
好的
Okay.
不是我说粗话 但你能赚多少钱
Not to be brash, but how much money do you make?
你在多大程度上考虑过这个问题
How far have you thought this through?
你能在经济上支持我吗
Are you gonna be able to financially support me?
因为如果你要成为我的男人
Because if you're gonna be my man,
假设我不能工作了
assuming that I'm not gonna be able to work,
而且我真的想要孩子
and I really want children.
你有吗
Do you?
嗯
Um...
嗯 我从我的祖母那里继承了一大笔钱
Well, I'm inheriting a good sum of money from my grandmother.grandmother.
多少钱
How much?
嗯
Um...
大约80万美金
About $800,000.
哇 那是 呃
Wow, that's, uh...
这是一个很大的
That's a lot.
这是一个严重的好生活
That's a seriously good life.
嗯 那是
Well, it's...
好吧 我宁愿拥有她
Well, I'd rather have her.
你知道
You know...
我确实相信你是个好人
I do believe that you're a good guy.
我是的
I am.
我很高兴我们能这样做
I'm glad we're doing this.
我们接下来做什么
What do we do next?
嗯 嗯
Mm. Well...
接下来你会操我
Next you would fuck me.
然后在接下来的几个星期里 你会再操我
And then over the next few weeks, you would fuck me again,again,
然后你就会感到厌烦
and then you'd get bored,
或者你不想认真起来
or you wouldn't want to get serious,
所以你就开始放松了
so you would just start easing out.
我永远不会对你失去兴趣
I'm never gonna lose interest in you.
穿着白缎子的夜晚
♪ Nights in white satin ♪
从未到达终点
♪ Never reaching the end ♪
我写过的信
♪ Letters I've written ♪
从未想过要寄出
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
来吧
Come on.
呃 我不知道怎么跳舞
Uh, I don't know how to dance.
是时候学习了
It's time to learn.
用这双眼睛前
♪ With these eyes before ♪
只是真相是什么
♪ Just what the truth is ♪
我不能再说了
♪ I can't say anymore ♪
因为我爱你
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
是的 我爱你
♪ Yes, I love you ♪
哦 我多么爱你
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
凝视着人们
♪ Gazing at people ♪
有些人手牵着手
♪ Some hand in hand ♪
我觉得很傻
I feel stupid.
我觉得自己真的很傻
I feel really stupid.
尽情享受吧
Just enjoy yourself.
你把我搂在怀里
You've got me in your arms.
有些人试图告诉我
♪ Some try to tell me ♪
他们无法辩护的想法
♪ Thoughts they cannot defend ♪
只是你想成为什么
♪ Just what you want to be ♪
你终究会成为
♪ You will be in the end ♪
我也爱你
♪ And I love you ♪
是的 我愛你
♪ Yes, I love you ♪
把你的衣服脱掉
Take your clothes off.
这样可以吗
Is this okay?
是的
Yes.
现在吻我
Now kiss me.
把你的舌头伸向我的
Touch your tongue to mine.
道格
Doug...
什么事
Yeah?
我必须告诉你一些事情
I have to tell you something.
那么 作为一个妓女是什么感觉
So what's it like being a hooker?
呃 我不是一个妓女
Uh, I'm not a hooker.
你认为自己是什么
What do you consider yourself?
嗯
Um...
我
I...
罗西
Rosy...
你有一个飞来横祸
You have a flyaway.
给你
There you go.
你认为自己是什么
What do you consider yourself?
我想 我更像是一个女主人
I'm more of a hostess, I guess.
你可以为我的陪伴付费
You can pay me for my company,
或者你根本不需要付钱给我
or you don't have to pay me at all,
但我感谢你的鼓励
but I appreciate the encouragement.
如果你相信我 你可以为一个班级或其他东西付钱
You could pay for a class or something
如果你相信我
if you believe in me.
如果你不喜欢我晚上独自走路回家 你可以给我买辆车
And if you don't like me walking home alone at night, you can buy me a car.night, you can buy me a car.
对我来说 听起来像一个妓女
Sounds like a hooker to me.
不过 是吗
Is it, though?
因为我不一定要和一个人睡觉
Because I'm not necessarily gong to sleep with a person.person.
除非他们让你值得去做
Not unless they make it worth your while?
不是
No.
我只和我想出去的男人约会
I only go out with the men I want to go out with,
我只和我想睡的人睡觉
and I only sleep with the men I want to sleep with,
无论他们是否送我礼物
whether or not they're giving me gifts.
你一晚上赚得最多的是什么
What's the most you made in one night?
一万块钱
Ten grand.
真的吗
Really?
哇 你做了什么才值得这样
Wow! What did you have to do to deserve that?
好吧
Okay.
我不想再这样做了
I don't wanna do this anymore.
罗西 坐下来吧
Rosy, take a seat.
你想这样做的 我们来做吧
You wanted to do this. Let's do it.
求你了
Please.
我只想和你在一起
All I want is to be with you.
罗西
Rosy...
- 来吧 - 为什么不呢
- Come on. - Why not?
我付钱给你
I pay you.
我喜欢这一点的原因
What I like about this
是我们不必担心它会变成什么
is that we don't have to worry about what it's gonna become.become.
但你为了我离开了你的妻子
But you left your wife for me.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那和我们没有任何关系
That didn't have anything to do with us.
我不能带你回家见我女儿
I can't take you home to meet my daughter.
你明白我的意思吗
Do you understand me?
不明白
No.
听着
Look...
你为什么要这样做
Why do you do it?
因为我可以
Because I can.
现在 一切都对你开放
Right now, everything is open to you,
但你没有选择任何东西
but you're not choosing anything.
你只是在等待被选择
You're just waiting to be chosen.
作为一个女演员
As an actress,
作为你在外面做的任何其他事情
as whatever else that you're out there doing.
好的
Okay.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
罗西 等等
Rosy, wait.
我认为我们不应该再见到对方了
I don't think we should see each other anymore.
不 不
No.
在你走之前 把这些穿上
Just before you go, put these on.
我不需要它们
I don't need them.
它们让我感觉更好
They make me feel better.
我们已经向前迈出了一大步
We've taken a huge step forward.
我穿上这些只是在倒退
Me putting those on would just be going backwards.
求你了
Please.
你当初为什么不约我出去
Why didn't you ask me out in the first place?
你永远不会给我一个机会
You would have never given me a chance.
呣
Mm.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你很奇怪
You're being weird.
你对我告诉你的事感到不安吗
Are you upset about what I told you?
没有
No.
那有什么问题吗
What's wrong, then?
其他男人是什么样的
What are other men like?
他们让你做了什么
What did they make you do?
有没有人伤害过你
Did anyone ever hurt you?
听着 这都是过去的事了
Look, it's in the past.
你很难过
You are upset.
这不是最容易吞下的事情
It's not the easiest thing to swallow.
你一定经历了一些非常艰难的事情
You must have been going through some pretty hard stuffstuff
才能经历这样的事情
to go through something like that.
我不知道 我只是
I don't know. I just...
对我来说 现在有很多事情需要处理
It's a lot for me to process right now.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
罗西
Rosy!
该死的 罗西 他妈的给我回来
Damn it, Rosy! Get the fuck back here!
嗷
Ow!
等等 等等
Wait! Wait!
求你了
Please!
救命啊
Help!
不
No!
救命啊
Help!
救命啊 救命啊
Help! Help!
- 不 - 嘘
- No! - Shh!
我相信你
I trusted you.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
平底锅还是起泡锅
Flat or sparkling?
起泡的 谢谢
Sparkling, please.
你看起来很迷人
You look fetching.
你认识那个人吗
You know that guy?
谁
Who?
就是你刚才看的那个人
The guy right over there who you just looked at.
我 呃 我不知道你在说什么
I, uh, I don't know what you're talking about.
哦 那就是同意了
Oh, so that's a yes.
这是给你的菜单
Here's the menus for you.
- 谢谢你 - 这是你的 女士
- Thank you. - Here you go, miss.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 噢 噢 - 喔噢 喔噢
- Oh! Oh! - Whoa! Whoa!
你他妈的跟我开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
- 我很抱歉 - 没事
- I'm sorry. - It's fine.
别担心 意外发生了 而且
Don't worry. Accidents happen, and...
你知道吗 我喜欢玻璃破碎的声音
You know what? I love the sound of breaking glass.
我会找人把它清理干净的
I'll get someone to clean that up.
我也喜欢玻璃破碎的声音
I also like the sound of breaking glass.
这他妈的是什么意思
What the fuck does that mean?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
请找些东西来清理一下吧
Just get some stuff to clean this up, please.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我可以带你到别的地方去吗
Can I take you somewhere else?
这个地方太荒谬了
This place is ridiculous.
为什么 我喜欢这个地方
Why? I like this place.
你只是嫉妒我的前任在这里
You're just jealous that my ex is here.
前任和客户是不一样的
An ex isn't the same thing as a client.
他不是我的客户
He wasn't my client.
他是我的前任
He's my ex.
你为什么要假装不认识他
Why did you pretend not to know him?
因为我知道 你会不高兴的
Because I knew that you would be upset.
太好了 一个护送者和一个女演员
Great. An escort and an actress.
嘿
Hey!
要么我是偏执狂 要么我是对的
Either I'm paranoid or I'm right.
现在你看起来嫉妒了
Now you look jealous.
这只是意味着你关心
That just means that you care.
不 我没有吃醋
No, I'm not jealous.
而且没有什么好谈的 这很好
And there's nothing to talk about. It's fine.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Really? - Really.
很好吗
It's fine?
很好
Fine.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
彼得
Peter.
我们为什么不邀请彼得来这里和我们一起吃饭呢
Why don't we invite Peter over here to join us for dinner?dinner?
别说了
Stop.
如果他不是客户 那有什么大不了的
If he's not a client, then what's the big deal?
为什么你总是对我这么可怕
Why are you always being so horrible to me?
他是你的朋友 你们应该谈谈
He's your friend. You guys should talk.
- 赶上了 - 不 不
- Catch up. - No. No.
- 彼得 - 你当真吗
- Peter? - Seriously?
彼得 听着 我不知道你是罗西的一个好朋友
Peter. Look, I didn't realize you were a good pal of Rosy's,Rosy's,
你为什么不过来和我们一起喝一杯
and why don't you come over here and join us for a drink?drink?
你应该为自己感到羞愧
You should be ashamed of yourself.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
求你了 我不是故意的
Please! I didn't mean to.
我不是故意要这样做的
I didn't mean to do this.
我不是故意的 我很抱歉
I didn't mean to. I'm sorry!
我真的很抱歉 求你了
I'm so sorry. Please.
你真的夹到了自己
You really did clip yourself.
我想你应该等上一段时间再回去砍柴
I think you should wait a while before you go back to chopping wood.to chopping wood.
有什么办法可以让我多请几个晚餐服务吗
Is there any way I could take off a few more dinner services?services?
我没有时间给那些不认真工作的人
I don't have time for people who don't take work seriously.seriously.
我只是觉得这不是我想继续做的事
I just don't feel like this is what I wanna keep doing,doing,
当你雇用我的时候 你说你会把我培养成一个厨师
and when you hired me, you said that you'd work me up to being a cook.up to being a cook.
是的 好吧 考虑到过去几个月事情的发展情况
Yeah. Well, considering how things have been going for the past couple of months,for the past couple of months,
那是相当丰富的
that's pretty rich.
先生 我想我不干了
Sir, I think I quit.
道格
Doug.
我可以解释一切
I can explain everything.
看着我 道格
Look at me, Doug.
嗳
Oi!
我在这里 你不能永远无视我
I'm here! You can't ignore me forever!
我要叫上一整天
I'm gonna scream all day long!
操
Fuck!
操你妈 操
Fuck you! Fuck!
来吧
Come on!
你为什么不长点胆量呢
Why don't you grow some balls for once!
你要听我说
You're gonna listen to me!
你这个该死的混蛋
You motherfucking arsehole!
你在跟谁说话
Who were you talking to?
哦 我
Oh. I...
好吧 让我看看你的手 让我看看你的手
All right. Let me see your hand. Let me see your hand.hand.
求你了 请帮助我 我发烧了 我感觉不是很好
Please. Please help me. I have a fever. I'm not feeling very well.feeling very well.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我需要一个医生
I need a doctor.
求你了
Please.
罗西
Rosy...
罗西 罗西
Rosy. Rosy?
你喜欢玻璃破碎的声音
You like the sound of breaking glass.
好吧 如果我给你一个医生
All right, if I get you a doctor,
你得配合我说你是我女朋友 好吗
you gotta play along that you're my girlfriend, okay?
会有一些严重的问题
There's gonna be some serious issues.
我是你他妈的女朋友
I am your fucking girlfriend!
嘿 嘿 嘿 你到底是怎么了
Hey, hey, hey! What the hell's the matter with you?
道格 你到底在做什么
Doug? What the hell are you doing?
你吓 你把我吓得半死
You scared... You scared me half to death.
我真的需要你帮助的东西
I really need your help with something.
这是一个医学问题
It's a medical thing.
还有 呃
And, uh...
这是我的女朋友
It's my girlfriend.
你好
Hello.
你们好
Hello there.
我是戈丁医生
I'm Dr. Godin.
你好
Hi.
我是罗西
I'm Rosy.
你还好吗 罗西
Are you all right, Rosy?
呃 让我看看我们这里有什么
Uh, let's see what we have here.
啊 好吧 这个
Ah, well, this...
这是很可怕的感染
This is terribly infected.
你为什么不把这个女孩带到医院 道格
Why haven't you brought this girl to the hospital, Doug?Doug?
这是很严重的
This is very serious.
- 嗯 - 我不想去
- Um... - I didn't wanna go.
我拒绝了
I refused.
我很害怕医院
I'm afraid of hospitals.
而且我没有保险
And I don't have insurance.
嗯 你知道 感染是这个国家的主要死因
Well, you know, infections are the leading cause of death in this country.death in this country.
你不会想失去这条腿的
You don't wanna lose this leg.
嗯 嗯 嗯
Mm-mmm.
没事的 没事的 没事的
It's all right. It's all right.
我们会照顾好它的
We're gonna take care of it.
什么 这里到底发生了什么
What... What exactly happened here?
我在森林里滑倒了
I slipped in the forest.
是的
Yeah.
哦
Oh.
你也害怕针头吗
Are you afraid of needles too?
不怕
No.
拿着这个
Hold that.
好的
All right.
好了 好了
深呼吸
Deep breath.
那里
There.
我拿着这个
I'll take that.
哦 什么
Oh, what...
你手腕上的伤痕是什么
What are the bruises on your wrists from?
是性
Sex.
是性爱造成的
It's from sex.
你们俩在一起多久了
How long have you two been together?
呃 几个月了
Uh, a few months.
但我们是非常认真的
But we're very serious.
嗯 我的妻子和我订婚了
Well, my wife and I got engaged
五个月后
after five months.
- 你们还在一起吗 - 噢
- Are you still together? - Oh...
今年六月已经十九年了
Nineteen years this June.
这不是我一生中最幸福的时光吗
Ain't it the happiest years of my life?
这是个笑话
It's a joke.
我只是在开玩笑
I was just joking.
我一生中的挚爱
The love of my life.
她是我一生的挚爱
She is the love of my life.
你有孩子吗
Do you have children?
是的 两个女儿和我的儿子
Yes, two daughters and my boy.
罗西想要孩子
Rosy wants children.
大多数女人都这样
Most women do.
我准备写一些处方
I am going to write some prescriptions
让你马上去取
for you to pick up right away.
你姓什么 罗西
What is your last name, Rosy?
你能不能把处方寄给我而不是她
Is there any way you could just make them out to me
而不是她 因为我的药剂师
instead of her? Because my pharmacist is
因为我的药剂师很喜欢让我去拿不属于我的药
really crazy about letting me pick up medication that's not mine.that's not mine.
- 呃 - 是的
- Uh... - Yes.
而且我不能去
And I can't go,
因为我病得很重
because I'm too ill.
我不能走路
I can't walk.
我真的不能这样做
I really can't do that.
姓什么
Last name?
这不是什么大问题 你可以直接给我做出来
It's not a big deal. You could just make it out to me.me.
就这样做吧
Just do it.
就这么办吧
我会告诉你什么
I'll tell you what.
如果他们给你一个问题 你只是给我打电话
If they give you a problem, you just give me a call.
好吗 你姓什么
All right? What is your last name?
嗯 她实际上是用了我的姓
Well, she actually took my last name,
因为我们刚刚结婚 还没有告诉任何人
'cause we just got married and we haven't told anybody yet.anybody yet.
你知道 打破大新闻
You know, break the big news.
好吧
Well...
祝贺你
congratulations.
这是伟大的
That's great.
那么 罗丝-兰德维尔
So, Rose Landver?
罗丝-兰德维尔
Rosy Lanver.
- 兰德维尔 - 兰德维尔
- Landver. - Landver.
兰德维尔
Landver.
好的
All right.
就让它响吧
Just let it ring.
好的
All right.
我们走吧
Here we go.
你准备好开车送我回去
You ready to drive me back?
你的垫子上是什么
What is that on your pad?
- 什么 - 我刚看到你记事本上写了些东西
- What? - I just saw something written on your pad.
我只是 我
I just... I...
处方药收据
Prescription receipt.
我们要不要 我们可以走了吗
Shall we... Shall we go?
是的 戈丁医生
Yeah, Dr. Godin?
是的 道格
Yeah, Doug.
我可以问你一些事情吗
Can I ask you something?
- 说吧 - 这是
- Shoot. - Here's...
你觉得我是个奇怪的人吗
Do you think I'm a strange guy?
事实上 我是这么认为的
I do, as a matter of fact.
你认为我有什么问题吗
Do you think there's something wrong with me?
我应该去看治疗师吗
Should I see a therapist?
你想让我给你推荐一个人吗
Would you like me to recommend you someone?
嗯
Um...
我是说 我只是
I mean, I just...
我想让你猜猜我的问题是什么
I want you to guess what's my issue.
我真的说不上来
I really couldn't say.
我很乐意给你推荐一个人
I'm happy to refer you to someone...
我有这种恐惧 害怕别人对我的看法
I have this fear of what people are thinking of me
而且我有一些事情 比如说这该死的思想漩涡
and I have things like just this fucking spirals of thought.thought.
还有 呃
And, uh...
每当我离开家的时候 它就会发生在我身上
And it just happens to me every time I leave the house every fucking day.house every fucking day.
这真的让我很不爽
This really fucks me up.
我只是想弄清楚它是什么
I'm just trying to figure out what it is.
我会给你找一个好的人
I'll find you someone good.
戈丁博士
Dr. Godin...
是吗
Yeah?
你有什么婚姻建议给我们吗
You got any marriage advice for us?
哦
Oh...
他们说 这有助于有一个短暂的记忆
They say it helps to have a short memory.
嗯 嗯 除此之外还有什么建议吗
Mm-hmm. Anything else besides that?
说实话
Honestly...
我认为 呃
I think, uh,
我学到的最重要的东西是
the most important thing I have learned is
关系是艰苦的工作
relationship is hard work.
你是什么意思
How do you mean?
呃 人们
Uh, people...
你知道 人们期望爱情能让事情变得简单
You know, people expect love to make things easy.
生活并不容易
Life's not easy.
但当你们
But it feels good when you...
一起度过难关的感觉很好
get through hard stuff together.
所以
So...
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢你
Thanks. Thank you.
真的 我现在要回家了
Really. I have to go home now.
你先请 我们走吧
After you. Let's go.
保重 罗西
Take care, Rosy.
道格
Doug...
Doug!
嘿 医生 还有一件事
Hey, Doc. One more thing.
是吗
Yeah?
你做了什么
What have you done?
你看你做了什么
You see what you did?
- 我做了什么 - 你又想耍我
- What did I do? - You tried to fuck me over again.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你想告发我
You tried to turn me in.
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
这张纸上写着 "俘虏"
It says "captive" on one of these papers.
我看到了 你在其中一张纸上写了 "俘虏"
I saw, you wrote "captive" on one of these papers,
它就在这里的某个地方 我会找到它的
and it's somewhere in here and I'm gonna find it.
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
它在哪里 他对它做了什么
Where is it? What did he do with it?
它在哪里 它在哪里
Where is it? Where is it?
我需要你帮我埋葬尸体
I need you to help me bury the body.
有人知道他来过这里吗
Does anyone know that he came here?
一、二、三
One, two, three...
起来 起来
Up, up.
好了 听着 我很抱歉
All right, listen. I'm sorry
关于我和你之间发生的事情
about what happened with me and you.
我真的很生气
I got really upset,
因为你说 你需要处理我告诉你的事情
because you said that you needed to process what I told you.told you.
什么
What?
这意味着你 你不信任我
Which means you, you don't trust me.
而我 我是一个值得信任的人
And I, I am a trustworthy person.
你用斧头打我的头
You hit me in the head with an ax.
- 不 从技术上讲我 - 是的 是的 你打了
- No. technically I... - Yeah, yeah. You did.
你用斧头直接打了我的头
You hit me straight in in the head with an ax.
不 我是用斧头柄刺中了你的头
No, I jabbed you in the head with the ax handle.
我知道 错误的举动
I know. Wrong move.
只是我太着急了 我太急于求成了 我很抱歉
It's just I got over-anxious and I jumped the gun. I'm sorry.I'm sorry.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你怎么能这样对我
How could you do this to me?
我的大脑告诉我逃跑 而我的心告诉我留下
My brain tells me to run, and my heart tells me to stay.stay.
我的意思是 你怎么能指望我驾驭这样的局面
I mean, how do you expect me to navigate a situation like this?like this?
你他妈的小点声
Keep your fucking voice down.
只是我得等你准备好
It's just I have to wait for you to be ready.
我只是
I just...
觉得我已经走了这么远 然后你拒绝了我
felt that I had come so far, and then you rejected me!me!
我还觉得你用我的过去来评判我
I also felt that you judged me about my past.
我从未评判过你
I never judged you.
那是你的问题
That's your issue.
你说你必须要处理一些事情
You said that you had to process things
才知道你是否还能爱我
before you knew if you could still love me.
不 我需要处理的是你是否真的爱我的想法
No, I needed to process the idea that you could actually love me.actually love me.
呃 我不是这种人
Uh... I'm not this kind of person.
- 我知道 - 这一切都不是我的本意
- I know. - I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
我只是
I'm just...
我只是一个人
I'm just a guy who...
谁 你知道 有一个非常困难的时间与事情
who, you know, has a really hard time with things.
而且
And...
这没关系的 来吧 只是
It's okay. Come on, just...
哭一哭 让它过去
Just cry and get it over with.
呃
Uh...
道格
Doug...
你曾经喜欢过我吗
Did you ever like me?
是的
Yes.
我喜欢你
I love you.
妈的
Fuck!
罗西
Rosy!
哦 我们又来了
Oh, here we go again!
绕来绕去 我们走
Round and round we go!
为什么我不惊讶呢
Why am I not surprised?
你又一次在背后捅了我一刀
Another time you stabbed me in the back!
你他妈的在背后捅了我一刀
You stabbed me in the fucking back.
我看到了你的枪
I saw your gun!
你要向我开枪
You were gonna shoot me.
哦 这就对了
Oh, that's right.
一切都是对我所做事情的反应 嗯
Everything is a reaction to what I do, huh?
这都是我的错
It's all my fault.
都是我的错
It's all my fault!
罗西
Rosy!
Rosy.
你知道 我喜欢你伤害我
You know, I like it when you hurt me.
我喜欢它 因为它使我对你的吸引力越来越小
I like it because it makes me less and less attracted to you,attracted to you,
这让我更容易接受
which makes this a whole lot easier for me.
因为你不是我想的那个人
Because you're not who I thought you were.
你知道 警察不会停止给我打电话
You know, the police won't stop calling me.
我为你杀了一个人 他被埋在地下了
I killed a guy for you, he's in the ground.
我是为了你才这么做的
I did that for you.
我甚至为你杀了我的祖母
I even killed my grandmother for you.
而你伤了我的心
And you broke my heart!
你伤了我的心
You broke my heart!
即使你伤了我的心
And even though you broke my heart,
我还是无法停止对你的思念
I can't stop thinking about you.
我不能睡觉 不能吃饭
I cannot sleep, I cannot eat.
我什么都不能做
I can't do anything.
我是一个烂摊子
I'm a mess.
我爱上了你
I'm in love with you!
I'm in love with you.
该死的
Goddamn it.
我知道你和那些男人在做什么
I knew what you were doing with those men.
我找过你 我跟踪了你
I looked you up. I followed you.
我只是想保护你不受伤害
I just wanted to protect you from yourself.
我知道我永远不会伤害你
I knew that I would never hurt you.
啊 他妈的
Ah, fuck.
我应该得到比这些更好的东西
I deserve better than all of this!
你根本不关心我
You don't care about me.
你只是把我占为己有
You just took me for yourself.
你根本不关心我的生活
You don't give a shit about my life.
你喜欢你的生活吗
Did you like your life?
哦 你怎么敢
Oh! How dare you?
我还在搞清楚这一切
I'm still figuring it all out.
开枪打我吧
Just shoot me.
动手吧
Do it.
向我开枪
Shoot me.
你对不起
You sorry...
我爱你 罗西
I love you, Rosy.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
亲爱的 我已经
♪ My darling, I've ♪
渴望着你的爱
♪ Been starving for your love ♪
亲爱的 我已经
♪ My darling, I've ♪
渴望着你的爱
♪ Been starving for your love ♪
请说出口 我将留下
♪ Please say. I'll stay ♪
再多待一会儿 我不会游离
♪ For a little longer. I won't stray ♪